let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does html stand for ....",
        answer: "C. hypertext markup language",
        options:[
            "A. hypertext mark language",
            "B. hypertest make language",
            "C. hypertext markup language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What tag is used to display a picture in html?",
        answer: "C. img",
        options:[
            "A. picture",
            "B. image",
            "C. img"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How can you make a bulleted list ?",
        answer: "B. ul",
        options:[
            "A. list",
            "B. ul",
            "C. nl"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How can you write into HTML output using JavaScript ?",
        options:[
            "A. Using innerHTML",
            "B. Using Console.log()",
            "c. Using document.write()"  
        ],
        answer: "c. Using document.write()"
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " b tag makes the enclosed text bold. What is other tag to make text bold?",
        options:[
           "A. strong",
           "B. emp",
           "c. i" 
        ],
        answer: "A. strong"
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "There are __ heading tags in html?",
        answer: "C. 6",
        options:[
            "A. 2",
            "B. 5",
            "C. 6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What does the .com domain represent ?",
        answer: "B. Commercial domain",
        options:[
            "A. Educational domain",
            "B. Commercial domain",
            "C. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What does Vlink attribute mean ?",
        answer: "A. visited Link",
        options:[
            "A. visited Link",
            "B. Virtual link",
            "C. good link"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about CSS?",
        answer: "A. CSS is the acronym for Cascading Style Sheet",
        options:[
            "A. CSS is the acronym for Cascading Style Sheet",
            "B. CSS is used to control the style of a web document in a simple and easy way",
            "c. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is a component of CSS style rule ?",
        answer: "B. Property",
        options:[
               "A. Selector",
               "B. Property",
               " c. Value"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which of the following selector matches all elements of a type?",
        answer: "A. The Type Selector",
        options:[
               "A. The Type Selector",
               "B. The Universal Selector",
               "C. The Descendant Selector"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Which of the following defines a measurement in inches?",
        answer: "A. in",
        options:[
            "A. in",
            "B. mm",
            "C. pc"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Which of the following defines a measurement in millimeters?",
        answer: "B. mm",
        options:[
            "A. in",
            "B. mm",
            "C. pc"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which of the following defines a measurement in picas?",
        answer: "C. pc",
        options:[
            "A. in",
            "B. mm",
            "C. pc"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Which of the following defines 1% of viewport height?",
        answer: "B. vh",
        options:[
            "A. px",
            "B. vh",
            "C. vw"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Which of the following defines a measurement in screen pixels?",
        answer: "A. px",
        options:[
            "A. px",
            "B. vh",
            "C. vw"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "which method is used to change text to uppercase ?",
        answer: "A. .touppercase()",
        options:[
            "A. .touppercase()",
            "B. .toString",
            "c. .tolowerCase"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Which method changes a string to number ?",
        answer: "A. Number()",
        options:[
           "A. Number()",
           "B. .toNumber",
           "c. Numbers()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Which attribute is used to name an element uniquely ?",
        answer: "B. id",
        options:[
            "A. class",
            "B. id",
            "c. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: " What tag creates a check box for a form in html ?",
        answer: `A. input type="checkbox"`,
        options:[
            `A. input type="checkbox"`,
            "B. input checkbox",
            "c. input = checkbox"
        ]
    }
];
